homestayin.com 2013-12-26

# Homestay - Find homestay families and book homestay accommodation - HomestayIn

####  1\. Collection of Personal Information

##### A. Boundary of personal information collection

First, Homestayin.com collects the personal information stated below in the member registration process to offer registration, host-guest communication, customer counseling, and other related services.

<Host>

  * \- Name, Sex, Age, ID, Password, Contact(E-mail, Mobile phone), Address, Profile photo

<Guest>

  * \- Name, Sex, Age, ID, Password, Contact(E-mail, Mobile phone), Profile photo

Second, some of the information may be gathered automatically from your use of our website services.

  * \- IP Address, Cookie, Log information, Unusual access records

Third, some credit card information can be collected automatically during your use of our paid services.

  * \- • Credit card company, Credit card number 

##### B. Information collection method

Homestayin.com collects personal information through member registration and modification process at the website.

####  2\. Purpose of Collection and use of personal information

##### A. Fulfillment of Service Contract & Billing of Service Fee

Offering contents for host & guest promotion, Providing contact details and address details of host and guest after booking confirmation, Offering matching information, Sending out invoices and bills, Verifying user identity, Purchasing and paying

##### B. Member management

Verifying user identity, Preventing fake members and unauthorized use, Checking intention of joining, Restricting registration and number of registrations, Verifying legal representative identity, Preserving records and documents for dispute settlements, Responding to user requests and Delivering notices

##### C. Development of new service(s) & Application to marketing and promotion

Developing new services, Offering matching services, Promoting based on demographic characters, Checking the effectiveness of services, Providing events and promotion information and offering chances of customer participations, Identifying log-in frequency, and Building statistics for members’ use of services

####  3\. Sharing & Offering Personal Information

Homestayin.com uses personal information only within the boundary stated in Article 2. Purpose of collection and use of personal information, and does not share or utilize any personal information beyond the boundary without consent from users unless one of the following circumstances applies:

  * \- When you have given prior consent in advance
  * \- When there is any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request 

####  4\. Consignment of Personal Information

Homestayin.com does not consign personal information of users to any third party.

####  5\. Storing and Using Period of Your Personal Information

In principle, Homestayin.com destroys personal information when the purpose of collection and use them are achieved. However, information stated below will be stored for designated time periods.

##### A. Storing of information due to internal regulations of Homestayin.com

  * \- Unusual/Illegal Usage Records 
    * Reason for storing: To prevent illegal access/usage 
    * Storing period: 1 year (365 days)

##### B. Storing of information due to related laws and government regulations

When related laws and government regulations such as Commercial Law and Consumer Protection Law in E-commerce require storing of information and data, Homestayin.com conforms to them. However, Homestayin.com stores information and data for respective purposes defined in each law or government regulation only. Please refer to the details stated below: 

  * \- Records of Contracts and Withdrawal of Subscription 
    * Reason for storing: Consumer Protection Law in E-commerce
    * Storing period: 5 years 
  * \- Records of Payment & Supply of Goods/Services 
    * Reason for storing: Consumer Protection Law in E-commerce
    * Storing period: 5 years
  * \- Records of Consumer Complaints / Dispute Resolution 
    * Reason for storing: Consumer Protection Law in E-commerce
    * Storing period: 3 years
  * \- Records of Self-Identification 
    * Reason for storing: Information Communication Promotion & Information Protection Law
    * Storing period: 6 months
  * \- Records of Website Visit/Log-in 
    * Reason for storing: Communication Confidentiality Protection Law
    * Storing period: 3 months

####  6\. Process and Method of Personal Information Destruction

In principle, Homestayin.com destroys personal information when the purpose of collection and use them are achieved. The process and method of Homestayin.com’s personal information destruction are as follow: 

##### A. Destruction Process

  * - The personal information which you entered for member registration will be transferred to a separate DB(printed documents will be moved to other filing cabinet) and stored for designated time period(please refer to Article 5. Holding and Using Period of Your Personal Information) to be destroyed.
  * - Those stored personal information will not be used in other purposed, unless enforced by related legal requirements.

##### B. Destruction Method

  * \- Printed personal information will be either shredded or incinerated.
  * \- Electronic personal information will be deleted in the non-reversible way.

####  7\. Rights of Users and Legal Representatives

  * - Users can always check or change their personal information. Users can also refuse to agree or even withdraw membership if they do not agree on the privacy policy of Homestayin.com. In that case, please be kindly reminded that users may have difficulty in using some or entire services offered by Homestayin.com.
  * - Users click on ‘Modify’ button for searching and changing personal information, or click on ‘Withdraw’ to terminate membership.
  * - Or you can also contact the manager in charge of privacy information directly, who will take necessary measures immediately.
  * - If you request for modification of personal information, your personal information is neither used nor given to other parties. If your pre-modification information has already been given to the third party, the modified information will be directly sent to the third party.
  * - Hpmestayin.com deals with information terminated or deleted by users or their legal representatives, according to Article 5. Holding and Using Period of Your Personal Information. Homestayin.com makes sure that those information are seen or used for purposes stated in the article only.

####  8\. Installation/Operation of Automatic Personal Information Collecting Tool

##### A. What is cookie?

  * - The Homestayin.com website uses ‘cookie’ which saves and load user information to provide personalized and matching services to users.
  * - A cookie is a small text file sent by a web server to user’s computer, and it is placed on the hard disk. When the user visits the website, the web server reads the information of cookies so that previously customized web browser setting for the specific user can be maintained.
  * - • Cookies do not collect personally identifiable information automatically/actively. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to user’s computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to each user, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to the respective user. Users can always refuse to save cookies or delete them.

##### B. Purpose of Cookies

  * - Homestayin.com uses cookies for two purposes; 
    * ① to understand users’ visit/usage pattern within the Homestayin.com website, popular search keyword, security access, news clipping, and no. of users
    * ② to provide users with the optimal customized information based on such understandings

##### C. Installation/Maintenance and Refusal of Cookie

  * - You have the right to accept or decline cookies. Thus you can allow all cookies, or check whenever cookie is saved, or even refuse all cookies, by adjusting the setting options in your web browser.
  * - However, if you choose to decline cookie, you may experience some difficulties in using some of Homestayin.com services which require member log-in.
  * - Please see below for setting/changing cookie installation policy. 
    * ① Click ‘Internet Option’ in [Tool] menu.
    * ② Click [Personal Information].
    * ③ Adjust [Level of Handling Personal Information].

####  9\. Technical/Managerial Protection of Personal Information

Homestayin.com works hard to prevent unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information as follows:

##### A. Password encryption

The password of Homestayin.com member ID is encrypted, saved, and managed. Even the internet security manager at Homestayin.com does not know the password. Only respective member who knows the password can check and change his or her personal information.

##### B. Counter-hacking measures

Homestayin.com strives to prevent personal information from disclosure or damage due to hacking or computer viruses. Homestayin.com regularly backs up personal information, uses most up-to-date vaccine program, and transmits information through encrypted communication. Homestayin.com also controls unauthorized access by using blocking system and other technical tools.

##### C. Limiting the number of employees dealing with personal information & Training

Homestayin.com restricts access to personal information to selected employees only. For management of personal information, Homestayin.com sets and renews special password. Also Homestayin.com conducts regular training for those selected employees to emphasize the importance of personal information security.  
We restrict access to personal information to Google employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations. 

####  10\. Personal Information Manager & Contact Point

You can send all the enquiries regarding personal information used in Homestayin.com website to Personal Information Manager’s e-mail. The manager will be contacting you with necessary information and authority to deal with your concerns.

For notification or consultation of other privacy violations, please contact organizations and government agencies stated below.

  * \- Center for Privacy Violation ([www.118.or.kr](http://www.118.or.kr/) / 118)
  * \- Online Privacy Association ([www.eprivacy.or.kr](http://www.eprivacy.or.kr/) / 82-2-580-0533~4) 
  * \- Supreme Prosecutors’ Office ([http://www.spo.go.kr](http://www.spo.go.kr/) / 82-2-3480-2000) 
  * \- National Police Agency ([www.ctrc.go.kr](http://www.ctrc.go.kr/) / 82-2-392-0330) 

####  11\. Duty of Declaration

Homestayin.com will declare and notify its users when there are changes in this privacy policy at least 7 days prior to modification at ‘Notice’ menu in the website. However, if changes in privacy policy involve critical elements such as Collection & Use of Personal Information or Provision of Information to the Third Party, Homestayin.com will declare and notify its users at least 30 days prior to modification.

  * \- Notice of Privacy Policy: July 1th, 2012
  * \- Initiation of Privacy Policy: July 1th, 2012
